{"data":[{"question":"There are a few shops _____ the end of the street.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- We say  \"on the way\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you going away on holiday _____ summer?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- In: used to name the book, document, film etc where something or someone appears","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Patricia doesn't usually go out _____ night.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"The same data can be found _____ different servers","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- We often say \"at home: stay at home, be at home\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We're moving house ____ two months.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"There's somebody ____ the door.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Did you see all the apples _____ that tree?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"The last bus leaves _____ 12:25 a.m.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you doing anything special _____ New Year?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"The television is ____ the living room.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"}]}